vanns.com 2015-09-05

# Vanns.com™ | Privacy Policy Statement

---  
| 

Home > Privacy Policy

| | |   
---|---|---  
| 

Vanns.com™ Privacy Policy Statement 

This is a web site of Vann's Acquisition LLC, the Internet Company of Vann's Acquisition LLC

Our postal address is:  
Vanns's Acquisition LLC  
Wells Fargo Tower  
1 East Broward Blvd STE 1605  
Ft Lauderdale, Florida   
33301

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [sales@vanns.com](mailto:sales@vanns.com)

Vanns.com™ has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. Finally, we will never share or sell your personal information, including your email address, to other companies for any reason, except as required by law.

## Information Automatically Logged

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's IP address/ Domain name combination. We collect IP Address/ Domain Name combination of visitors to our Web page and aggregate information on what pages consumers’ access or visit.

## Cookies  

Our Site uses cookies to save your customer number. This allows our site to automatically customize your shopping experience. The cookie does not gather any information from your computer or profile your system. We do not store any personal information within our cookies.

## Registration Forms

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information such as their name, email, and postal address. We will never share or sell your personal information, including your email address, to other companies for any reason, except as required by law. Contact information from the registration forms is used to enhance the customer interaction in the site. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out here. Unique identifiers such as a customer number are automatically generated by our system. 

## Order Forms

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We securely collect financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

## External Links

This site contains links to other sites. Vanns.com™ is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such external Web sites.

## Security

Vanns.com™ site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Additionally, ordering and financial information is sent encrypted to our servers using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology is presently the safest way to send credit card information over the Internet. Information is first encrypted on your computer, and then decrypted on our side, preventing anyone from accessing any information in between.

## Use of Information

The information that you provide to Vanns.com™ can and may be used for the following purposes including, but not limited to: Tracking and confirming online orders, product deliveries, providing various customer services, administering promotions or surveys, sending marketing communications, fulfilling requests made by you, and performing other business activities as needed.

## Sharing of Information

Vanns.com™ will never sell your personal information, including your email address, to other companies for any reason. However, we may need to share some of your personal information with other companies to provide services such as shipping or delivery.

Additionally, we may share information with select partners, service providers or others acting on our behalf for limited purposes. Examples of the types of services for which we may share personal information with partners include, but are not limited to: Delivering packages, sending marketing communications, scheduling and performing installation services, sending mail or email on behalf of Vanns.com™ , processing credit card payments, or servicing products.

Any third party partner with whom Vanns.com™ conducts business and that is authorized to use your information is: Only allowed to use your information to perform the service for which they are hired, must abide by the terms of our privacy policy, must take reasonable measures to protect any shared information, and must comply with any applicable legal requirements regarding the privacy of your information.

Updated 07/2014

|   
| |   

|   
---
